interface Lesson {
    id: number,
    question: string,
    romanized: string,
    answer: string | string[]
  }

export const vietnameseWords: Lesson[] = [
    {
      id: 0,
      question: "và",
      romanized: "và",
      answer: "and"
    },
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "là",
      romanized: "là",
      answer: "is"
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "tôi",
      romanized: "tôi",
      answer: "I"
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "bạn",
      romanized: "bạn",
      answer: "you"
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "của",
      romanized: "của",
      answer: "of"
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "nó",
      romanized: "nó",
      answer: "it"
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "chúng tôi",
      romanized: "chúng tôi",
      answer: "we"
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "trong",
      romanized: "trong",
      answer: "in"
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "có",
      romanized: "có",
      answer: "have"
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "không",
      romanized: "không",
      answer: "no"
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "với",
      romanized: "với",
      answer: "with"
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "một",
      romanized: "một",
      answer: "one"
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "người",
      romanized: "người",
      answer: "person"
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: "cho",
      romanized: "cho",
      answer: "for"
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: "ở",
      romanized: "ở",
      answer: "at"
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: "cái",
      romanized: "cái",
      answer: "thing"
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: "trên",
      romanized: "trên",
      answer: "on"
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: "đó",
      romanized: "đó",
      answer: "there"
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: "anh",
      romanized: "anh",
      answer: "he"
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: "ra",
      romanized: "ra",
      answer: "out"
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: "như",
      romanized: "như",
      answer: "like"
    },
    {
      id: 21,
      question: "em",
      romanized: "em",
      answer: "she"
    },
    {
      id: 22,
      question: "cũng",
      romanized: "cũng",
      answer: "also"
    },
    {
      id: 23,
      question: "những",
      romanized: "những",
      answer: "those"
    },
    {
      id: 24,
      question: "đến",
      romanized: "đến",
      answer: "to"
    },
    {
      id: 25,
      question: "nhìn",
      romanized: "nhìn",
      answer: "look"
    },
    {
      id: 26,
      question: "thấy",
      romanized: "thấy",
      answer: "see"
    },
    {
      id: 27,
      question: "đi",
      romanized: "đi",
      answer: "go"
    },
    {
      id: 28,
      question: "lại",
      romanized: "lại",
      answer: "again"
    },
    {
      id: 29,
      question: "rồi",
      romanized: "rồi",
      answer: "already"
    },
    {
      id: 30,
      question: "nếu",
      romanized: "nếu",
      answer: "if"
    },
    {
      id: 31,
      question: "chỉ",
      romanized: "chỉ",
      answer: "only"
    },
    {
      id: 32,
      question: "nhưng",
      romanized: "nhưng",
      answer: "but"
    },
    {
      id: 33,
      question: "lời",
      romanized: "lời",
      answer: "words"
    },
    {
      id: 34,
      question: "khi",
      romanized: "khi",
      answer: "when"
    },
    {
      id: 35,
      question: "từ",
      romanized: "từ",
      answer: "from"
    },
    {
      id: 36,
      question: "họ",
      romanized: "họ",
      answer: "they"
    },
    {
      id: 37,
      question: "này",
      romanized: "này",
      answer: "this"
    },
    {
      id: 38,
      question: "biết",
      romanized: "biết",
      answer: "know"
    },
    {
      id: 39,
      question: "qua",
      romanized: "qua",
      answer: "through"
    },
    {
      id: 40,
      question: "nói",
      romanized: "nói",
      answer: "say"
    },
    {
      id: 41,
      question: "chúng",
      romanized: "chúng",
      answer: "they"
    },
    {
      id: 42,
      question: "về",
      romanized: "về",
      answer: "about"
    },
    {
      id: 43,
      question: "tới",
      romanized: "tới",
      answer: "to"
    },
    {
      id: 44,
      question: "muốn",
      romanized: "muốn",
      answer: "want"
    },
    {
      id: 45,
      question: "sẽ",
      romanized: "sẽ",
      answer: "will"
    },
    {
      id: 46,
      question: "con",
      romanized: "con",
      answer: "child"
    },
    {
      id: 47,
      question: "việc",
      romanized: "việc",
      answer: "work"
    },
    {
      id: 48,
      question: "dưới",
      romanized: "dưới",
      answer: "under"
    },
    {
      id: 49,
      question: "bên",
      romanized: "bên",
      answer: "beside"
    },
    {
      id: 50,
      question: "thì",
      romanized: "thì",
      answer: "then"
    },
    {
      id: 51,
      question: "vào",
      romanized: "vào",
      answer: "into"
    },
    {
      id: 52,
      question: "đây",
      romanized: "đây",
      answer: "here"
    },
    {
      id: 53,
      question: "còn",
      romanized: "còn",
      answer: "still"
    },
    {
      id: 54,
      question: "lên",
      romanized: "lên",
      answer: "up"
    },
    {
      id: 55,
      question: "sau",
      romanized: "sau",
      answer: "after"
    },
    {
      id: 56,
      question: "năm",
      romanized: "năm",
      answer: "year"
    },
    {
      id: 57,
      question: "đại",
      romanized: "đại",
      answer: "great"
    },
    {
      id: 58,
      question: "bị",
      romanized: "bị",
      answer: "by"
    },
    {
      id: 59,
      question: "phải",
      romanized: "phải",
      answer: "must"
    },
    {
      id: 60,
      question: "lớn",
      romanized: "lớn",
      answer: "big"
    },
    {
      id: 61,
      question: "nhỏ",
      romanized: "nhỏ",
      answer: "small"
    },
    {
      id: 62,
      question: "cùng",
      romanized: "cùng",
      answer: "together"
    },
    {
      id: 63,
      question: "nhận",
      romanized: "nhận",
      answer: "receive"
    },
    {
      id: 64,
      question: "hơn",
      romanized: "hơn",
      answer: "more"
    },
    {
      id: 65,
      question: "trước",
      romanized: "trước",
      answer: "before"
    },
    {
      id: 66,
      question: "thế",
      romanized: "thế",
      answer: "so"
    },
    {
      id: 67,
      question: "gì",
      romanized: "gì",
      answer: "what"
    },
    {
      id: 68,
      question: "nên",
      romanized: "nên",
      answer: "should"
    },
    {
      id: 69,
      question: "điều",
      romanized: "điều",
      answer: "thing"
    },
    {
      id: 70,
      question: "đều",
      romanized: "đều",
      answer: "all"
    },
    {
      id: 71,
      question: "được",
      romanized: "được",
      answer: "get"
    },
    {
      id: 72,
      question: "mình",
      romanized: "mình",
      answer: "self"
    },
    {
      id: 73,
      question: "tất",
      romanized: "tất",
      answer: "all"
    },
    {
      id: 74,
      question: "ông",
      romanized: "ông",
      answer: "he"
    },
    {
      id: 75,
      question: "đời",
      romanized: "đời",
      answer: "life"
    },
    {
      id: 76,
      question: "mới",
      romanized: "mới",
      answer: "new"
    },
    {
      id: 77,
      question: "nước",
      romanized: "nước",
      answer: "water"
    },
    {
      id: 78,
      question: "luôn",
      romanized: "luôn",
      answer: "always"
    },
    {
      id: 79,
      question: "lòng",
      romanized: "lòng",
      answer: "heart"
    },
    {
      id: 80,
      question: "giữa",
      romanized: "giữa",
      answer: "between"
    },
    {
      id: 81,
      question: "nhà",
      romanized: "nhà",
      answer: "home"
    },
    {
      id: 82,
      question: "cả",
      romanized: "cả",
      answer: "both"
    },
    {
      id: 83,
      question: "nay",
      romanized: "nay",
      answer: "today"
    },
    {
      id: 84,
      question: "chưa",
      romanized: "chưa",
      answer: "not yet"
    },
    {
      id: 85,
      question: "lúc",
      romanized: "lúc",
      answer: "time"
    },
    {
      id: 86,
      question: "tự",
      romanized: "tự",
      answer: "self"
    },
    {
      id: 87,
      question: "vì",
      romanized: "vì",
      answer: "because"
    },
    {
      id: 88,
      question: "lại",
      romanized: "lại",
      answer: "back"
    },
    {
      id: 89,
      question: "chỗ",
      romanized: "chỗ",
      answer: "place"
    },
    {
      id: 90,
      question: "ngày",
      romanized: "ngày",
      answer: "day"
    },
    {
      id: 91,
      question: "mỗi",
      romanized: "mỗi",
      answer: "each"
    },
    {
      id: 92,
      question: "thời gian",
      romanized: "thời gian",
      answer: "time"
    },
    {
      id: 93,
      question: "đứng",
      romanized: "đứng",
      answer: "stand"
    },
    {
      id: 94,
      question: "cần",
      romanized: "cần",
      answer: "need"
    },
    {
      id: 95,
      question: "lần",
      romanized: "lần",
      answer: "time"
    },
    {
      id: 96,
      question: "giờ",
      romanized: "giờ",
      answer: "hour"
    },
    {
      id: 97,
      question: "xem",
      romanized: "xem",
      answer: "watch"
    },
    {
      id: 98,
      question: "tình",
      romanized: "tình",
      answer: "love"
    },
    {
      id: 99,
      question: "điện thoại",
      romanized: "điện thoại",
      answer: "telephone"
    }
  ];
  